

Suva Akash Mohanty



suvaakash28@gmail.com



9337102475

TECHNICAL SKILL

- Microsoft Word
- Microsoft Excel
- · Microsoft Powerpoint
- Basic Filmora
- · Basic Python

LANGUAGE

- ENGLISH
- Hindi
- Odia

MY DETAILS

- D.O.B -03/08/2001
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/suvaakash-mohanty-732017276
- 🔹 🏺 Jaleswar , Balasore

PROFILE

lam an energetic, ambitious person who has developed a mature and responsible approach to any task that I undertake , or situation lam presented with . As a graduate with 3 year experience, lam excellent in working others to achieve a certain objective on time and with excellence .

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Vocation in Tourism and Hospitality management, Fakir Mohan Autonomous College, Balasore (2022) -

- Academic Marks: 75.88%
- Involvement in many Placement Cell and Fest Committee

12th,Fakir Mohan Junior College, Balasore (2018) -

• Academics Marks: 65.16%

10th, Swami Nigamananda High School, Jaleswar (2016) -

Academic Marks: 84.66%

EXPERIENCE

Organisation: Arpita Beach Resort, Chandipur, Balasore as Duty Manager (Full Tme Internship From DEC 2021 - JAN 2023)-Roles and Responsibility -

- To communicate with upper management to stay up to date with organisational issues and improvements.
- To watch over daily operations, ensuring employee productivity.
- To supervise, guiding and coordinate the employees work while general managers are awaay.
- To create a positive work environment for employees
- Working as a freelancer as a content writer, copywriter and email copy writer since March 2020
- Working as a Private Tutor, specializing in subjects such as English and Social Studies since April 2021

Internships Experience (Bachelor Degree) Successfully completed total 1 year Internship by National Skill Development Corporation(NSDC) during graduation

- Guest Relation Manager Intern in Barjorjis Hotel, Fakir Mohan Golei, Balasore (FEB 2019-APRIL 2019)
- Front Office Associate Intern in Barjorjis Hotel, Fakir Mohan Golei, Balasore(FEB 2021-APRIL 2021)
- Front Office Executive Intern in Arpita Beach Resort, Chandipur, Balasore(SEPT 2021-NOV 2021)
- Duty Manager Intern in Arpita Beach Resort, Chandipur, Balasore (JAN 2022-MARCH 2022)

CERTIFECATION

- Information Technology by Odisha State Open University , Sambalpur, Odisha .
- Advance Macro Economics and Mutual Fund by Shine Project (Online)
- Financial Market by Shine Project(Online)
- Fundamentals of Digital Marketing by Google